<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<doc>
  <source><![CDATA[https://starwars.fandom.com/ru/wiki/2010_%D0%B3%D0%BE%D0%B4]]></source>
  <category verify="true" type="str" auto="true">Фантастика</category>
  <title verify="true" type="str" auto="true"><![CDATA[2010 год]]></title>
  <keywords verify="true" type="list" auto="true">
    <item type="str"><![CDATA[Годы (реальный мир)]]></item>
    <item type="str"><![CDATA[2010 год]]></item>
  </keywords>
  <text verify="true" type="str" auto="true"><![CDATA[Список событий 2010 года, связанных со вселенной «Звёздных войн».
Январь
01 — «The Clone Wars»: «Grievous Intrigue» and «The Deserter» aired.
01 — «Rebel Force: Trapped» released.
01 — «Star Wars: Heroes» released.
06 — «Star Wars: The Clone Wars 12: Hero of the Confederacy, Part 3» released.
07 — «Star Wars: The Clone Wars: Day One» released.
13 — Star Wars: Knights of the Old Republic: Destroyer trade paperback released.
13 — «Omnibus: Shadows of the Empire» released.
19 — «Галактика интриг» released.
20 — «Star Wars: Dark Times 15: Blue Harvest, Part 3» released.
20 — «Star Wars: Knights of the Old Republic 49: Demon, Part 3» released.
22 — The Clone Wars: «Lightsaber Lost» aired.
26 — «Поперечное течение» released.
26 — Star Wars Miniatures: The Dark Times released.
27 — «Star Wars: Legacy 44: Monster, Part 2» released.
28 — «Войны клонов. Решай свою судьбу: Кризис на Корусанте» released.
28 — «The Clone Wars: Decide Your Destiny: Dooku's Secret Army» released.
28 — «Stand Aside — Bounty Hunters!» released.
28 — «Star Wars: The Clone Wars: Holocron Hunters» released.
29 — The Clone Wars: «The Mandalore Plot» aired.
Февраль
03 — «Star Wars Adventures Volume 3: Luke Skywalker and the Treasure of the Dragonsnakes» released.
05 — The Clone Wars: «Voyage of Temptation» aired.
10 — «Затерянное племя ситхов: Соперники» released.
10 — Star Wars: Legacy: Tatooine trade paperback released.
12 — The Clone Wars: «Duchess of Mandalore» aired.
17 — «Star Wars: Knights of the Old Republic 50: Demon, Part 4» released.
21 — Star Wars Galaxy Series 5 released.
23 — «Войны клонов. Гамбит: Невидимка» released.
24 — «Star Wars: Legacy 45: Monster, Part 3» released.
Март
09 — «Backlash» released.
12 — The Clone Wars: «Senate Murders» first aired in Canada.
13 — The Clone Wars: «Senate Murders» aired in the UK.
16 — «Threat of the Conqueror», the seventh expansion of the Star Wars Galaxies Trading Card Game released.
19 — The Clone Wars: «Senate Murders» aired in the US.
20 — The Clone Wars: «Cat and Mouse» first aired in the UK.
24 — «Omnibus: Boba Fett» released.
25 — «Старая Республика: Авангард контрабандистов» released exclusively on StarWars.com.
26 — The Clone Wars: «Cat and Mouse» aired in the US.
27 — The Clone Wars: «Bounty Hunters» aired in the UK.
31 — «Star Wars: Legacy 46: Monster, Part 4» released.
Апрель
01 — «Star Wars: The Clone Wars: Children of the Force» released.
02 — эфир эпизода «Охотники за головами» в США.
03 — эфир эпизода «Зверь Зилло» в Великобритании.
06 — издание «Star Wars Miniatures: Masters of the Force».
07 — публикация комикса «Звёздные войны. Чистка: Скрытый клинок».
09 — эфир эпизода «Зверь Зилло» в США.
10 — эфир эпизода «Зверь Зилло наносит ответный удар» в Великобритании.
14 — публикация комикса «Звёздные войны. Тёмные времена 16: Голубой урожай, часть 4».
16 — эфир эпизода «Зверь Зилло наносит ответный удар» в США.
17 — эфир эпизода «Смертельная ловушка» в Великобритании.
20 — публикация книги «Справочник по Неизведанным Регионам».
23 — эфир эпизода «Смертельная ловушка» в США.
23 — умер Эйдзи Кусухара.
24 — эфир эпизода «R2, лети домой» в Великобритании.
27 — «Затерянное племя ситхов: Спаситель» released.
27 — публикация «Rebel Force: Uprising».
28 — публикация сборника Star Wars: Invasion: Refugees (TPB).
28 — публикация комикса «Звёздные войны. Наследие 47: Судьба Дака».
30 — эфир эпизода «R2, лети домой» в США.
30 — эфир эпизода «Смертельные поиски».
Май
01 — «Star Wars: Head-to-Head» released.
03 — «Join the Rebels» released.
12 — «Star Wars: A Scanimation Book» released.
13 — «Star Wars: The Clone Wars: Bounty Hunter: Boba Fett» released.
21 — 30th anniversary of «Star Wars Episode V: The Empire Strikes Back».
23 — Family Guy: Something, Something, Something, Dark Side aired.
25 — «Allies» released.
25 — «Omen» paperback released.
26 — «Star Wars: Legacy 48: Extremes, Part 1» released.
26 — «Star Wars: Invasion 6: Rescues, Part 1» released.
31 — «Death Star Battles» released.
Июнь
01 — «Fire Ring Race» released.
01 — «Shinbone Showdown» released.
03 — «Omnibus: A Long Time Ago... Volume 1» released.
16 — Star Wars The Clone Wars: In Service of the Republic trade paperback released.
16 — Star Wars: Knights of the Old Republic: Demon trade paperback released.
22 — «Star Wars: The Clone Wars Character Encyclopedia» released.
22 — «Abyss» paperback released.
30 — «Star Wars: Dark Times 17: Blue Harvest, Part 5» released.
30 — «Star Wars: Invasion 7: Rescues, Part 2» released.
30 — «Star Wars: Legacy 49: Extremes, Part 2» released.
30 — Star Wars: Legacy: Monster trade paperback released.
Июль
01 — «Star Wars: The Clone Wars: Padawan Puzzles» released.
01 — «Star Wars: The Clone Wars: Legacy of Terror» released.
06 — «Войны клонов. Гамбит: Осада» released.
07 — «Star Wars: The Old Republic 1: Threat of Peace, Part 1» released.
19 — «Star Wars Blueprints: Rebel Edition» released.
20 — «Star Wars: The Old Republic: Fatal Alliance» released.
21 — «Star Wars Adventures Volume 4: The Will of Darth Vader» released.
22 — «Star Wars: The Clone Wars: The Hunt for Grievous» released.
22 — «Star Wars: The Clone Wars Secret Missions 2: Curse of the Black Hole Pirates» released.
28 — «Star Wars: Invasion 8: Rescues, Part 3» released.
Август
04 — «Star Wars: The Old Republic 2: Threat of Peace, Part 2» released.
12-15 — Celebration V held.
12-15 — «Star Wars: Knight Errant 0» handed out at Celebration V.
12 — «Star Wars: Tales from the Clone Wars» debuted.
16 — «Star Wars: The Clone Wars: Jedi Heroes» released.
16 — «Star Wars: The Clone Wars: Planets in Peril» released.
16 — «Star Wars Year by Year: A Visual Chronicle» released.
18 — «Star Wars: Legacy» ended with «Star Wars: Legacy 50: Extremes, Part 3».
25 — «Star Wars: Blood Ties: A Tale of Jango and Boba Fett, Part 1» released.
30 — «Star Wars: The Clone Wars: New Battlefronts: The Visual Guide» released.
Сентябрь
01 — «Star Wars The Clone Wars: Hero of the Confederacy» released.
01 — «Star Wars: The Old Republic 3: Threat of Peace, Part 3» released.
15 — «Star Wars: Clone Wars Adventures» released.
15 — «Star Wars: Dark Empire Trilogy» released.
17 — The Clone Wars: Season Three began with the episodes «Clone Cadets» and «ARC Troopers».
22 — «The Sounds of Star Wars» released.
24 — The Clone Wars: «Supply Lines» aired.
28 — «Дарт Бэйн: Династия зла» paperback edition released.
28 — «The Jedi Path: A Manual for Students of the Force» released.
29 — «Omnibus: A Long Time Ago... Volume 2» released.
29 — «Star Wars: Blood Ties: A Tale of Jango and Boba Fett, Part 2» released.
29 — Star Wars: The Force Unleashed II comic released.
29 — «Star Wars: Invasion 9: Rescues, Part 4» released.
30 — «Star Wars: The Clone Wars Official Episode Guide Series 1 & 2» released.
Октябрь
01 — A special edition of «Star Wars: Visions» released.
01 — The Clone Wars: «Sphere of Influence» aired.
05 — The novelization of The Force Unleashed II released.
06 — «Star Wars: The Old Republic 4: Blood of the Empire, Part 1» released.
08 — The Clone Wars: «Corruption» aired.
12 — «The Making of The Empire Strikes Back» released.
13 — «Star Wars: Knight Errant 1: Aflame, Part 1» released.
15 — The Clone Wars: «The Academy» aired.
19 — «Star Wars: Knight Errant: Influx» released online at StarWars.com.
25 — «Затерянное племя ситхов: Чистилище» released.
22 — The Clone Wars: «Assassin» aired.
26 — «Star Wars: The Force Unleashed II» released.
26 — «Star Wars: The Clone Wars: The Complete Season Two» released.
26 — «Штурмовики смерти» paperback released.
26 — «Star Wars: The Force Unleashed II: Prima Official Game Guide» released.
27 — «Star Wars: Blood Ties: A Tale of Jango and Boba Fett, Part 3» released.
27 — «Star Wars: Invasion 10: Rescues, Part 5» released.
28 — «Star Wars: The Clone Wars: Defenders of the Republic» released.
28 — «Star Wars The Clone Wars: Villains» released.
28 — «UK Star Wars Galaxy issue 1» released.
Ноябрь
01 — публикация сборника «Star Wars: Visions».
03 — публикация комикса «Star Wars: The Old Republic 5: Blood of the Empire, Part 2».
05 — эфир эпизода «Зловещие планы».
10 — публикация комикса «Star Wars: Knight Errant 2: Aflame, Part 2».
12 — эфир эпизода «Охота на Зиро».
17 — публикация сборника «Star Wars: Dark Times: Blue Harvest».
19 — эфир эпизода «Герои на обеих сторонах».
24 — публикация комикса «Star Wars: Blood Ties: A Tale of Jango and Boba Fett, Part 4».
26 — публикация комикса «Star Wars: The Old Republic: Threat of Peace».
27 — скончался Ирвин Кершнер.
30 — публикация книги «Судьба джедаев: Вихрь».
Декабрь
01 — «UK Star Wars Galaxy issue 2» released.
02 — «Star Wars: The Clone Wars Volume 5: Deadly Hands of Shon-Ju» released.
02 — «Star Wars: The Old Republic 6: Blood of the Empire, Part 3» released.
02 — «Omnibus: Quinlan Vos: Jedi in Darkness» released.
03 — The Clone Wars: «Pursuit of Peace» aired.
08 — «Star Wars: Knight Errant 3: Aflame, Part 3» released.
08 — Star Wars: Legacy: Extremes TPB released.
14 — «The Price of Victory», the eighth set in the Star Wars Galaxies Trading Card Game, is released.
15 — «Star Wars: Legacy—War 1» released.
19 — «Robot Chicken: Star Wars Episode III» aired.
21 — «Family Guy: It's A Trap!» released on DVD.
22 — «Star Wars: Invasion 11: Rescues, Part 6» released.
27 — Grant McCune passes away.
28 — «Красная жатва» released.]]></text>
</doc>
